{"tossups": [{"question": "Supposed \"supplements\" to this text, published by Franc\u0327ois Nodot (noh-doh) and Jose\u0301 Marchena, were later shown to be forgeries. One man's description of his future tomb to the stonemason Habinnas in this text causes him, his wife, and an entire household to cry. This text ends with a man reading a will stating that only those who consume his body can be his heirs. In this text, the narrator's friend Ascyltos (as-KILL-tos) &amp;ees a speech being given outside a school and attempts to have sex with the narrator's lover. The poet Eumolpus (yoo-\"MOLE\"-pus) appears in this text, whose protagonists are tortured by followers of a cult of Priapus and are invited to a dinner hosted by the freedman Trimalchio (trih-MAHL-kee-oh). For 10 points, name this Roman text about Encolpius and his lover, Giton, that was written by Gaius Petronius Arbiter.", "answer": "Satyricon [or Satyricon liber]", "subcategory": "Classical Literature", "category": "Literature", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>Satyricon</u></b> [or <b><u>Satyricon liber</u></b>]", "acceptable": ["Satyricon", "Satyricon", "Satyricon liber"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "Hermann\u2013Mauguin notation is unusually preferred to Scho\u0308enflies (\"SHOW\"-un-flees) point group notation when using this technique. Isomorphous replacement of uranium improves this technique's results. The precision of this technique is reported as an \"R factor,\" which is a normalized difference in structure factors. The analyte is ground into a powder in the Debye\u2013Scherrer (deh-BYE SHUR-ur) form of it. Dorothy Hodgkin was a pioneer of this technique, which occurs in a goniometer (goh-nee-AH-met-ur) that spins the sample tube so that one can find the glide planes, the screw axes, and the Miller indices. The von Laue (vawn LAW-uh) and Bragg equations give mathematical backing for this technique, which is used to solve protein structures. For 10 points, name this analytical technique in which high-energy radiation diffracts through an ordered sample.", "answer": "X-ray diffraction [or XRD; or X-ray crystallography; prompt on \"diffraction\"]", "subcategory": "Biology", "category": "Science", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>X-ray diffraction</u></b> [or <b><u>XRD</u></b>; or <b><u>X-ray crystallography</u></b>; prompt on <u>diffraction</u>]", "acceptable": ["X-ray diffraction", "X-ray diffraction", "XRD", "X-ray crystallography"], "promptable": ["diffraction"], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "A Clifford Berryman cartoon analogizes one of this general's campaigns to Uncle Sam jumping a barbed-wire fence and grumbling \"I've had about enough of this.\" While stationed at Fort Bliss, this subordinate of Frederick Funston learned that his wife and children had died in a house fire. At a February 2016 campaign rally, Donald Trump repeated the debunked claim that this general dipped bullets in pig's blood while fighting Muslim rebels. In this general's highest post, he refused to deploy all-black regiments, such as the Harlem Hellfighters. After the town of Columbus, New Mexico, was attacked, this general led a \"Punitive Expedition\" to capture Pancho Villa. For 10 points, what commander of the American Expeditionary Force during World War I was nicknamed \"Black Jack\"?", "answer": "John Pershing [or John Joseph \"Black Jack\" Pershing; prompt on \"Black Jack\" before it is mentioned]", "subcategory": "American History", "category": "History", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>John Pershing</u></b> [or <b><u>John Joseph \"Black Jack\" Pershing</u></b>; prompt on <u>Black Jack\"</u> before it is mentioned]", "acceptable": ["John Pershing", "John Pershing", "John Joseph \"Black Jack\" Pershing"], "promptable": ["Black Jack\""], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "These organisms use the noncanonical amino acids B\u00c2\u00b7M\u00c2\u00b7A\u00c2\u00b7A and A\u00c2\u00b7D\u00c2\u00b7D\u00c2\u00b7A to make toxic microcystins (\"micro\"-SIS-tins). Species of these organisms are numbered in the Pasteur culture collection\u00c2\u2014for example, PCC 6803, which is a model organism. An icosahedral microcompartment first discovered in these organisms receives Ru\u00c2\u00b7B\u00c2\u00b7P through a capsid-like shell and converts it to 3-phospho\u00c2\u00b7glycerate. Stromatolites are biofilms composed mostly of these organisms. Lynn Margulis compared thylakoids to the carboxy\u00c2\u00b7somes and light-harvesting centers in this phylum. More than two billion years ago, these organisms caused the Great Oxygenation Event. Endosymbiosis predicts that chloroplasts originated as these organisms. For 10 points, name this phylum of photosynthetic bacteria o0en erroneously called blue-green algae.", "answer": "cyanobacteria [or cyanobacterium; accept blue-green algae before \"blue-green\"; prompt on \"bacteria\" or \"bacterium\" or \"prokaryotes\"; do not accept or prompt on \"algae\"]", "subcategory": "Biology", "category": "Science", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>cyanobacteria</u></b> [or <b><u>cyanobacterium</u></b>; accept <b><u>blue-green algae</u></b> before \"blue-green; prompt on <u>bacteria</u> or <u>bacterium</u> or <u>prokaryotes</u>; do not accept or prompt on \"algae\"]", "acceptable": ["cyanobacteria", "cyanobacteria", "cyanobacterium", "blue-green algae"], "promptable": ["bacteria", "bacterium", "prokaryotes"], "rejectable": ["algae"], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "A set of handscrolls illustrating this ruler's armies in battle shows the use of \"thunder crash bombs,\" an early form of explosive shell launched from catapults. To overcome a fear of this ruler, a leader consulted his religious adviser, Mugaku Sogen (moo-GAH-koo SOH-gen), who urged the leader to scream \"victory\" until his fear subsided. This ruler's &amp;eet was defeated at the Battle of Bach Dang (\"botch\" dahng) by the Tran dynasty, which later joined with the Champa kingdoms in accepting this man's supremacy over Vietnam. After annexing the Goryeo Kingdom, this ruler used Korean shipbuilders to prepare for an invasion spurred by Hojo Tokimune's (toh-kee-MOO-nay's) impudence. His fleets were twice destroyed by typhoons referred to as \"divine wind.\" Two failed invasions of Japan were ordered by, for 10 points, what first emperor of the Yuan dynasty?", "answer": "Kublai Khan [or Kubilai Khan; or Yuan Shizu]", "subcategory": "World History", "category": "History", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>Kublai Khan</u></b> [or <b><u>Kubilai Khan</u></b>; or <b><u>Yuan Shizu</u></b>]", "acceptable": ["Kublai Khan", "Kublai Khan", "Kubilai Khan", "Yuan Shizu"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "French artist ORLAN (or-LAHN) created an edgy, nearly identical version of this painting, renamed so that the last word of its title is \"war.\" Deborah de Robertis was arrested in 2014 for a piece of performance art that involved sitting in front of this painting in a gold dress. A modern parody of this work by Tanja Ostojic\u0301 (TAHN-yah oh-STOH-yitch) includes an article of clothing with the European Union &amp;ag on it. This painting, which was commissioned by Khalil Bey, was purchased in 1955 by the psychoanalyst Jacques Lacan. The recently discovered upper half of this work confirmed that its model was likely Joanna Hiffernan. Only one breast of this work's splay-legged subject is visible, as the other is covered by white fabric. For 10 points, name this painting by Gustave Courbet that depicts a woman's naked lower half.", "answer": "The Origin of the World [or L'Origine du monde]", "subcategory": "Visual Fine Arts", "category": "Fine Arts", "answer_formatted": "The <b><u>Origin of the World</u></b> [or <b><u>L'Origine du monde</u></b>]", "acceptable": ["The Origin of the World", "Origin of the World", "L'Origine du monde"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "When this goddess was refused from Rhodes, she drove the sons of Poseidon and Halia mad, causing them to rape their own mother and be buried alive as punishment. In the Odyssey, the Phaeacian (fee-AY-shan) bard Demodocus sings of the humiliation of this goddess, whose Homeric epithets include Philomeides (\"FIE\"-low-may-dees), or \"laughter-loving.\" Hera cursed this goddess to give birth to an ugly and impotent son whom she conceived with Dionysus. This goddess, the mother of the constantly erect god Priapus, entrusted Persephone with a chest holding a youth who had been born from a split myrrh tree, but she later feuded with Persephone over the boy's love. That youth, a lover of this goddess, was gored to death by Ares in the form of a boar. For 10 points, what lover of Adonis was the Greek goddess of love?", "answer": "Aphrodite [accept Venus until \"Greek\" is read]", "category": "Mythology", "subcategory": "Mythology", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>Aphrodite</u></b> [accept <b><u>Venus</u></b> until \"Greek\" is read]", "acceptable": ["Aphrodite", "Aphrodite", "Venus"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "Two married artists from this modern-day country documented the internal beauty of industrial structures by creating photographic typologies, presented in rectangular arrays, of visually similar gas tanks or water towers. Crowds at art museums were depicted in the series Museum Photographs by an artist from this country. Another artist from this country portrayed the horizontality of shelves laden with mass-produced products in his photographic diptych of a 99-cent store. Thomas Struth (toh-MAS STROOT) and Andreas Gursky are from this country, whose bombed-out capital appears in a photo of soldiers raising the Soviet &amp;ag above its national legislative building. Bernd and Hilla Becher were from, for 10 points, what country home to the Du\u0308sseldorf School and the Reichstag?", "answer": "Germany [or Federal Republic of Germany; or Bundesrepublik Deutschland]", "subcategory": "Other Fine Arts", "category": "Fine Arts", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>Germany</u></b> [or <b><u>Federal Republic of Germany</u></b>; or <b><u>Bundesrepublik Deutschland</u></b>]", "acceptable": ["Germany", "Germany", "Federal Republic of Germany", "Bundesrepublik Deutschland"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "This author drew a frontispiece for one of his novels in which a fool looks at his re&amp;ection in a cracked mirror. The Fairy Blackstick helps the true heirs of Pa&amp;agonia and Crim Tartary marry and distributes the title beauty-granting magical objects in one of this author's novels. This author coined the term \"Oxbridge\" in a novel whose title character marries his foster sister Laura Bell and refuses to take Sir Clavering's Parliament seat through blackmail. This author of The Rose and the Ring and The History of Pendennis created a woman who idealizes her husband George Osborne, who dies in the Waterloo Campaign. The anti-heroine of this man's \"novel without a hero\" marries Rawdon Crawley and befriends Amelia Sedley. For 10 points, what author created Becky Sharp in Vanity Fair?", "answer": "William Makepeace Thackeray", "subcategory": "British Literature", "category": "Literature", "answer_formatted": "William Makepeace <b><u>Thackeray</u></b>", "acceptable": ["William Makepeace Thackeray", "Thackeray"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "Each of these operations should have an associated converse limitation theorem called a tauberian theorem. Specially designed means are used in N\u00c3\u00b8rlund's, Abel's, and Cesa\u0300ro's methods for this operation. An integral with error terms given by Bernoulli numbers is equated to this operation by the Euler\u00c2\u2013Maclaurin formula. In one instance, zeta-function regularization and Ramanujan's example of this operation yield minus one-twel0h. One can obtain a value of one-half for Grandi's series, which consists of alternating plus-ones and minus-ones, by taking the arithmetic mean of partial examples of this operation. For 10 points, what operations assign a finite value to a divergent series and are symbolized by a big sigma because they should yield the expected result for a convergent series?", "answer": "summation methods for divergent series [or summability methods; accept regularization before \"regularization\"; accept equivalents such as assigning a value to a divergent series before \"assign\"]", "subcategory": "Math", "category": "Science", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>summation methods for divergent series</u></b> [or <b><u>summability methods</u></b>; accept <b><u>regularization</u></b> before \"regularization; accept <b><u>equivalents such as assigning a value to a divergent series</u></b> before \"assign]", "acceptable": ["summation methods for divergent series", "summation methods for divergent series", "summability methods", "regularization", "equivalents such as assigning a value to a divergent series"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "During this man's ministry, a bribery scandal arising out of the escape of convicted drug dealer Lucien Rivard brought about the resignation of his attorney general Guy Favreau. This prime minister's government set up the Laurendeau\u00c2\u2013Dunton Commission to study bilingualism and biculturalism. A0er he criticized the bombing of North Vietnam at Temple University, he was told by Lyndon Johnson not to \"come into my living room and piss on my rug.\" This successor to Louis St. Laurent as party leader accepted the Bomarc missile program and instituted universal healthcare. As the minister of external affairs, he won a Nobel Peace Prize for helping to resolve the Suez Crisis. For 10 points, what Liberal prime minister of Canada served in the 1960s and was succeeded by Pierre Trudeau?", "answer": "Lester Pearson [or Lester Bowles Pearson; accept Mike Pearson]", "subcategory": "World History", "category": "History", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>Lester Pearson</u></b> [or <b><u>Lester Bowles Pearson</u></b>; accept <b><u>Mike Pearson</u></b>]", "acceptable": ["Lester Pearson", "Lester Pearson", "Lester Bowles Pearson", "Mike Pearson"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "Sayings of and speeches by this man were collected by al-Sharif al-Radi. This man requested to be buried in secret so that his body wouldn't be desecrated by his enemies, so it is disputed whether he lies in Mazar-e-Sharif or Najaf. This man's words are collected in the Nahj al-Balagha, or Peak of Eloquence. A dispute about this man centers on the use of the term \"mawla,\" or \"master,\" in a proclamation issued near a pond in Ghadir Khumm. While this man was praying, a Kharijite wielding a poisoned sword assassinated him. He wielded the sword Zulfiqar (ZOOL-fee-kar) during his victories at Badr and Khaybar. Fatima was married to, for 10 points, what son-in-law of Muhammad who is considered by Shias to be the first imam and is recognized by Sunnis as the fourth of the rightly guided caliphs?", "answer": "Ali [or Ali ibn Abi Talib; or Ali bin Abi Talib]", "category": "Religion", "subcategory": "Religion", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>Ali</u></b> [or <b><u>Ali ibn Abi Talib</u></b>; or <b><u>Ali bin Abi Talib</u></b>]", "acceptable": ["Ali", "Ali", "Ali ibn Abi Talib", "Ali bin Abi Talib"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "This man conducted a study in which participants living near stairways were more likely to make friends on other &amp;oors; based on that study, he posited that \"propinquity,\" or proximity, was more important to forming friendships than shared beliefs or interests. Participants in another of this man's studies reported that a boring activity was more enjoyable when, after they completed the activity, they were paid a small amount, rather than a large amount, to tell another person that the activity wasn't boring. He is the alphabetically first author of a book profiling the \"Seekers,\" a UFO cult whose doomsday prediction did not come true. For 10 points, what psychologist devised the theory of cognitive dissonance and, with Henry Riecken and Stanley Schachter, wrote When Prophecy Fails?", "answer": "Leon Festinger", "category": "Social Science", "subcategory": "Social Science", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>Leon Festinger</u></b>", "acceptable": ["Leon Festinger", "Leon Festinger"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "Kaikhosru Sorabji (kai-KOHS-roo soh-RAHB-jee) retired from performing after premiering the second of his four pieces of this type. Aram Khachaturian (kah-chah-TOO-ree-ahn) wrote an E-&amp;at-minor piece of this type for solo piano that was meant to form a three-part suite with a waltz-capriccio and a dance. One piece of this type for piano begins with the hands alternating as they rapidly hit a D note. Robert Schumann said that the hardest composition ever written was his own Opus 7, a piece of this type. Charles-Marie Widor (SHAR-leh mah-REE VEE-dor) composed one of these pieces for the final movement of his Fi0h Organ Symphony. One piece of this type begins with a buildup to a diminished seventh chord and is the first section of a two-part piece featured in the opening of Fantasia. For 10 points, what type of piece was paired with a fugue in D minor by J. S. Bach?", "answer": "toccata", "subcategory": "Auditory Fine Arts", "category": "Fine Arts", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>toccata</u></b>", "acceptable": ["toccata", "toccata"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "This man wrote of a so-called painter who calls himself the \"final barber, the last beautician\" in one of 22 dramatic monologues spoken by Death in his collection Flight Among the Tombs. The German epigraph \"we have a law, and according to the law he must die\" precedes a poem by this man, which prophesies that a murdered boy \"will walk in as you're sitting down to a meal\" and is titled \"The Book of Yolek.\" The title figure in a poem by this man \"said one or two unprintable things\" after she was brought \"all the way down from London\" and addressed as a \"mournful cosmic last resort.\" This man wrote about a woman who \"had read Sophocles in a fairly good translation\" and thus caught the \"bitter allusion to the sea\" in a Matthew Arnold poem. For 10 points, what British poet wrote \"The Dover Bitch\"?", "answer": "Anthony Hecht [or Anthony Evan Hecht]", "subcategory": "British Literature", "category": "Literature", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>Anthony Hecht</u></b> [or <b><u>Anthony Evan Hecht</u></b>]", "acceptable": ["Anthony Hecht", "Anthony Hecht", "Anthony Evan Hecht"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "The citrus company Hanotea negotiated a deal with the German government on behalf of this movement, creating a financial transfer service called Haavara. An Okhrana (oh-KRAH-nah) agent based in Paris may have authored a document, purporting to outline this movement's operations, that heavily plagiarized a political satire by Maurice Joly (zhoh-lee). Joseph Chamberlain's Uganda Proposal offered this movement an alternative to its main goal of aliyah. In Britain, this movement was led by Chaim Weizmann (\"HIE\"-im VITES-mahn) and Walter Rothschild, the latter of whom received the Balfour Declaration. A forgery called the \"protocols\" of this movement's \"elders\" claimed that it was a plot to take over the world. For 10 points, name this movement led by Theodor Herzl that sought to establish a Jewish homeland in Israel.", "answer": "Zionism [accept forms of the word Zionist; prompt on Judaism]", "subcategory": "European History", "category": "History", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>Zionism</u></b> [accept <b><u>forms of the word Zionist</u></b>; prompt on <u>Judaism</u>]", "acceptable": ["Zionism", "Zionism", "forms of the word Zionist"], "promptable": ["Judaism"], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "In the Lorentz gauge, the inhomogeneous wave equation for phi has a right-hand side consisting of this quantity in the numerator. To find the scalar retarded potential, one integrates this quantity evaluated at the retarded time divided by the distance. In the static case, Jefimenko's equation for the electric field reduces to an integral of this quantity as a function of position. The negative time derivative of this quantity equals the divergence of J according to the current continuity equation. The differential form of Gauss's law sets the divergence of the electric field equal to this quantity divided by epsilon-nought. A triple integral of this quantity gives the total charge in a region. For 10 points, what quantity, typically denoted rho, is the amount of electric charge per unit of volume?", "answer": "electric charge density [accept rho before \"rho\"; prompt on \"density\" a0er \"charge\"; do not accept or prompt on \"density\" before \"charge\"]", "subcategory": "Physics", "category": "Science", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>electric charge density</u></b> [accept <b><u>rho</u></b> before \"rho; prompt on <u>density\" a0er \"charge</u>; do not accept or prompt on \"density\"\" before \"charge]", "acceptable": ["electric charge density", "electric charge density", "rho"], "promptable": ["density\" a0er \"charge"], "rejectable": ["density\""], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "One of this thinker's books argues that dreams, rather than perception or thoughts, are the \"primary phrase of consciousness\" in a chapter on \"First Steps and First Fluctuations\"; that book by this thinker defines its title concept as \"efficacious re&amp;ection\" and is subtitled \"The Phases of Human Progress.\" In another book, this thinker distinguished between intuition as pure absorption in \"essence\" and intuition in&amp;ected by \"intent\"; in that book, he argued that there is no firm epistemological foundation to build upward from because belief and nonbelief are both \"radically incapable of proof,\" so \"philosophy must begin in medias res.\" For 10 points, name this author of Skepticism and Animal Faith, who declared that \"those who cannot remember the past are doomed to repeat it.\"", "answer": "George Santayana [or Jorge Agusti\u0301n Nicola\u0301s Ruiz de Santayana y Borra\u0301s]", "category": "Philosophy", "subcategory": "Philosophy", "answer_formatted": "George <b><u>Santayana</u></b> [or <b><u>Jorge Agusti\u0301n Nicola\u0301s Ruiz de Santayana y Borra\u0301s</u></b>]", "acceptable": ["George Santayana", "Santayana", "Jorge Agusti\u0301n Nicola\u0301s Ruiz de Santayana y Borra\u0301s"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "In 1993, a Democratic member of this state's legislature sarcastically proposed an amendment banning property taxes; Republican legislators voted the amendment in, thereby defunding this state's entire public school system. A politician from this state was confused by Minnesota senator Al Franken's question about the difference between \"proficiency\" and \"growth\"; that politician from this state vowed to \"help advance God's Kingdom\" and claimed that children in Wyoming might need guns to defend themselves from bears. The most populous city in this state implemented charter-school reform under the guidance of Donald Trump's secretary of education, Betsy DeVos. For 10 points, what state's governor, Rick Snyder, declared a state of emergency during the Flint water crisis?", "answer": "Michigan", "category": "Current Events", "subcategory": "Current Events", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>Michigan</u></b>", "acceptable": ["Michigan", "Michigan"], "promptable": [], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "Because actions involving this substance and \"the Lip you press\" might \"end in the Nothing all Things end in,\" a poem suggests thinking that \"you are Today what Yesterday / you were\" and that \"tomorrow you shall not be less.\" This substance has \"play'd the Infidel\" and \"robb'd\" the speaker of his \"Robe of Honor.\" Although \"David's lips are locked,\" the \"Nightingale cries\" this word four times \"to the Rose.\" The addressee is urged to \"lose your fingers in the tresses of / the Cypress-slender minister\" of this substance. This liquid is mentioned in a quatrain that inspired the title of Eugene O'Neill's only comedy with the line \"ah, wilderness were paradise enow.\" Omar Khayyam writes of \"a Book of Verses underneath the Bough\" with a \"loaf of bread\" and a jug of, for 10 points, what liquid?", "answer": "wine [prompt on \"alcohol\" or similar answers]", "subcategory": "Other Literature", "category": "Literature", "answer_formatted": "<b><u>wine</u></b> [prompt on <u>alcohol</u> or <u>similar answers</u>]", "acceptable": ["wine", "wine"], "promptable": ["alcohol", "similar answers"], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}, {"question": "The \"pressure\" and \"materials\" gaps explain disparities in the rate of this process. This process occurs via creation of a surface vacancy in the Mars van Krevelen mechanism. In spheres, this process is described by the equation \"eta equals one over phi tanh (\"tanch\") three phi,\" where eta is this process's effectiveness factor and phi is the Thiele (TEEL-uh) modulus. The namesake base SI unit for the rate of this process is a mole per second. The Langmuir\u00c2\u2013Hinshelwood (LANG-mweer HIN-shul-\"wood\") mechanism assumes this process is limited by the rate of adsorption. The rate of this process is described by a turnover number. It occurs on zeolite beads in a packed-bed reactor in its heterogeneous form. For 10 points, name this process by which reactions are made to go faster by the lowering of their activation energy.", "answer": "heterogeneous catalysis [accept word forms; accept biocatalysis; accept reaction rate before \"reaction\"; prompt on answers mentioning the word \"enzyme\" (or word forms) but not the word \"catalyst(s)\"]", "subcategory": "Chemistry", "category": "Science", "answer_formatted": "heterogeneous <b><u>catalysis</u></b> [accept word forms; accept <b><u>biocatalysis</u></b>; accept <b><u>reaction rate</u></b> before \"reaction; prompt on <u>answers mentioning the word \"enzyme\" (or word forms) but not the word \"catalyst(s)</u>]", "acceptable": ["heterogeneous catalysis", "catalysis", "biocatalysis", "reaction rate"], "promptable": ["answers mentioning the word \"enzyme\" (or word forms) but not the word \"catalyst(s)"], "rejectable": [], "metadata": ""}], "bonuses": []}